

FRANCISCO **AGUIRRE**

FULL STACK DEVELOPER





Email

franmaguirre@gmail.com



Tel

+54 9 0351-156140453



C Link Portofolio



Ubicación

Ingeniero López 275, Córdoba, Argentina

PERFIL

Hola! Mi nombre es Francisco, soy Desarrollador Full Stack (Inglés-Castellano). Me apasiona la creación de diseños web escalables, responsivos y dinámicos que mejoren la experiencia del usuario y estimulen el crecimiento del negocio. Me encanta crear proyectos desafiantes utilizando programación funcional, orientados a facilitar el testing QA y la depuración en el proceso del ciclo de desarrollo.

EDUCACIÓN

2023

Python | Data Science **IBM Certification**

2022 - 2023

Full Stack .NET Developer

ISPC - Cba - Arg

2007 - 2012

Traductorado de Inglés

UNC - Cba - Arg

LENGUAJES DE PROGRAMACIÓN / **HERRAMIENTAS**

JavaScript (React | Angular)

Python (Django)

Java (Spring-Boot)

C# (.NET Framework)

HTML | CSS | GIT

SQL (SQL Server | MySQL |

PostgreSQL)

EXPERIENCIA LABORAL

Encode SA (Software Factory -Firma Digital)

2022 - 2023

- Escribir código limpio y probable usando lenguaje C# para back end, typescript para Front y SQL para gestión de bases de datos.
- Probar y depurar diversas aplicaciones de .NET.
- Revisar y refactorizar el código.

Proyectos Freelance

2021 - 2023

- https://franciscoaguirrefrontendapp.netlify.app
- https://franciscoaguirreauthlogin.netlify.app
- https://e-commerce-gatsby-francisco.netlify.app/
- https://blog-francisco.netlify.app/
- https://online-store-francisco.netlify.app/

Soporte Técnico Nivel - Encode 2021 - 2023 SA

- Soporte Técnico remoto para usuarios de firma digital.
- Configuración de sistemas operativos e instalación
- de paquetes y controladores.



FRANCISCO **AGUIRRE**

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



in Link LinkedIn



Email

franmaguirre@gmail.com



Cel phone

+54 9 0351-156140453





Location

Ingeniero López 275, Córdoba, Argentina

PROFILE

Hi! I'm Francisco, a Full Stack Software Developer with advanced english-spanish skills, I am passionate about developing innovative solutions that enhance user experiences and drive business growth. With a solid foundation in front-end and back-end development, I have experience building dynamic web applications and responsive mobile interfaces.

EDUCATION

2023

Python for Data Science IBM Certification

2022 - 2023

Full Stack .NET Developer Polytechnic Institute (Cba)

2007 - 2012

ENG-SP Translation -

National University at Córdoba

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES AND TOOLS

JavaScript (React | Angular)

Python (Django)

Java (Spring-Boot)

C# (.NET Framework)

HTML | CSS | GIT

SQL (SQL Server | MySQL |

PostgreSQL)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Encode (Software Factory - Digital Signature)

2022 - 2023

- C# / SQL / Angular
- Full stack Projects using C# for backend, SQL Server and Angular (Typescript) for frontend
- · Web API calls and microservices use

Freelance Projects

2021 - 2023

- https://franciscoaguirrefrontendapp.netlify.app
- · https://franciscoaguirreauthlogin.netlify.app
- https://e-commerce-gatsby-francisco.netlify.app/
- https://blog-francisco.netlify.app/
- https://online-store-francisco.netlify.app/

Technical Support -Encode 2021 - 2023 (Software Factory)

- Remote assistance for digital signature software clients
- · Operative systems setup and browser security configuration
- Packages installation procedures to ensure correct setup environment for our products